freetrafficsystem.com 2013-05-23

# Privacy Policy | Free Traffic System

FreeTrafficSystem.com has established this Privacy Policy to explain how it protects and manages the personal information that it collects from its users.

**1\. Consent for Collection, Use and Disclosure**

Your use of the FreeTrafficSystem.com site and/or your registration inside FreeTrafficSystem.com service constitute your consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the FreeTrafficSystem.com site and do not register in FreeTrafficSystem.com service.

FreeTrafficSystem.com may occasionally update this Privacy Policy on its personal consent, without prior notification to the FreeTrafficSystem.com service user about the changes.

FreeTrafficSystem.com also has the right not to inform and obtain the consent of the user, such as in connection with an investigation of a breach of an agreement, contravention of laws, an emergency where the life, health or security of an individual is threatened, the collection of a debt or in compliance with the request of a law enforcement agency or a court order.

FreeTrafficSystem.com user can stop his or her consent for collection, use and disclosure at any time by sending an email from web form on the Contact Us page of FreeTrafficSystem.com  web site. If you do, FreeTrafficSystem.com suspends its provision of the services to you.

**2\. Accountability**

FreeTrafficSystem.com collects, at the time of your registration and your sign-on to its web site, certain “personal information” (information that personally identifies you) including but not limited to your name, email address, blog accesses.

FreeTrafficSystem.com has implemented this Privacy Policy to protect personal information received from its customers, and to respond to any inquiries. The Privacy Policy also provides that FreeTrafficSystem.com will use appropriate contractual means to establish a comparable level of protection for personal information which is sent for processing by third parties on FreeTrafficSystem.com’s behalf.

**3\. Purposes for Collecting Personal Information**

FreeTrafficSystem.com collects and uses personal information for the following purposes:

(i) to allow customers to access limited-entry areas of FreeTrafficSystem.com’s site;

(ii) to communicate with customers and site visitors, when necessary, and to inform customers of upgrades, as well as of other products and services available from FreeTrafficSystem.com, its affiliates and third parties;

(iii) to develop and provide our web site and our products and services for our customers;

(iv) to fulfill your requests for products, services or information;

(v) to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or government request;

(vi) to respond to a legitimate claim, or to address our reasonable belief, that you are violating the rights of any third party or any of the agreements or policies that govern your use of the FreeTrafficSystem.com site or any FreeTrafficSystem.com product or service;

(vii) to protect the services, products or rights of FreeTrafficSystem.com, including but not limited to the security or integrity of the FreeTrafficSystem.com site; and

(viii) to identify and resolve technical problems concerning FreeTrafficSystem.com’s site, products and services.

FreeTrafficSystem.com also uses personal information in an aggregate form (i.e., not individually attributable to you) for its business analysis, operational, marketing and other promotional purposes.

If we hire other companies to provide some products or services on our behalf, then we will only provide those companies the personal information they need for the purposes mentioned in article 3 of this Privacy Policy, and we will limit their rights to use and further disclose your personal information as appropriate in the course of their work for us.

**4\. Limiting the Collection and Process of Collection of Personal Information**

FreeTrafficSystem.com limits its collection of personal information to only that information which is necessary for the purposed mentioned in article 3 of this Privacy Policy. FreeTrafficSystem.com does not direct its site to, nor does it knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen.

When you visit the FreeTrafficSystem.com web site, a cookie may be placed on your computer or the cookie may be read if you have visited the FreeTrafficSystem.com site previously.

FreeTrafficSystem.com uses cookies to allow FreeTrafficSystem.com track information as who exactly referred you to FreeTrafficSystem.com service. If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the FreeTrafficSystem.com web site, you may not be able to subscribe to certain service and product offerings on the FreeTrafficSystem.com site.

**5\. Disclosure, Processing and Retention**

FreeTrafficSystem.com does not sell, rent or disclose your personal information to anyone else, except:

(i) for any of the purposes mentioned in article 3 of this Privacy Policy;

(ii) to FreeTrafficSystem.com’s employees, independent contractors, subsidiaries, affiliates, consultants, business associates, service providers, suppliers and agents, acting on FreeTrafficSystem.com’s behalf for any of the purposes mentioned in article 3 of this Privacy Policy;

(iii) as necessary if FreeTrafficSystem.com has reason to believe that disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with FreeTrafficSystem.com’s rights or property, other users of FreeTrafficSystem.com’s web site, products or services, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities; and

(iv) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law.

In addition, as we continue to develop our business, we or our affiliates may sell or buy other businesses or entities, or we may merge with another company. In such transactions, personal information may be one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that FreeTrafficSystem.com or substantially all of its assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets.

Your information may be stored and processed in the United States, or in any other country in which FreeTrafficSystem.com or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities. By using this web site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

After your account becomes inactive (that is, if you request to be removed from our database), FreeTrafficSystem.com will keep your personal information in its archives. Your information will then be used only as necessary for tax reasons or to prove FreeTrafficSystem.com’s compliance with any applicable law or other reasons necessary to protect the rights of FreeTrafficSystem.com, its products and/or services.

**6\. Accuracy of Personal Information**

FreeTrafficSystem.com will use reasonable efforts to keep customer personal information accurate for purposes mentioned in article 3 of this Privacy Policy, and for minimizing the possibility of making inappropriate customer decisions based on such information. Customers are responsible for informing FreeTrafficSystem.com about changes to their personal information. You can do this by calling sending email from the web form on the Contact Us page of FreeTrafficSystem.com ****

**7\. Security Safeguards**

FreeTrafficSystem.com will use reasonable efforts to protect customers’ personal information. ****

**8\. Access to Personal Information**

FreeTrafficSystem.com gives you access to the personal information which is available on the online profile inside FreeTrafficSystem.com members area. You all get access to general information about your 1st and 2nd tier referrals and their posting activity which is relevant to your account in FreeTrafficSystem.com

Once you cancel your membership in FreeTrafficSystem.com you lose the right and access to your personal information inside the members area of FreeTrafficSystem.com
